statravel.com.sg 2016-10-16

# Privacy policy | STA Travel | Privacy policy

**What information we collect**

We will collect personal information that is relevant to your travel arrangements. This includes providing necessary information to airlines, tour companies, car hire agencies, hotels or insurance providers to fulfill your travel arrangements. By making a booking, you consent to STA Travel using any personal information for the purpose of making and completing travel arrangements on your behalf.

Promotions that run on our site may be sponsored by companies other than STA Travel, or may be co-sponsored. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the co-sponsor(s). If data collected is to be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

When you visit the STA Travel website, we may collect and store information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you looked at on our site and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We may also record the name of your Internet service provider. We only use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our site.

 **Who is collecting your information** When you are on the site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with STA Travel only except when explained in this privacy policy.

 **With whom such information will be shared**

When you make travel arrangements with STA Travel and provide information about yourself, we use this information to complete your travel arrangements and to provide you with promotional information. Some or all of the date collected during a promotion maybe shared with the co-sponsor(s).

STA Travel may disclose the information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to us or to others. We may also disclose your information when we believe the law requires it.

 **Opt in and opt Out** STA Travel puts the control over communication directly into your hands, where it belongs. We only send our latest breaking "goss" emails to you, if you ask to receive them.

We won't pester you with junk mail - promise! But if you'd like to be the first to find out about deals, then you will be required to complete an online registration form to join our e-newsletter. Your email address will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and it will not be added to a mailing list or used for any other purpose without your consent. We have provided you access to alteration and correction facilities so that you may change any of your details should they change.

We hate spam too. If you want to stop receiving our "special" emails, you can click on the Unsubscribe link in the email you've been sent and you'll automatically be removed from the mailing list.

 **ISIC card information** The information submitted to us is confidential. We do not sell it to anyone. We will only use the information that you supply for the purpose of verifying your cardholder status. Information and discounts are correct at time of printing and are subject to change without notice.

 **Third party links**  
  
The STA Travel site may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have no control. The information practices of those web sites are not covered by this privacy policy. Any information you provide to third party web sites will be governed under the terms of each such web site's privacy policy. We have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third party web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all third party web sites that link to this site because such privacy policies may be materially different from our privacy policy.

 **Security** You take online privacy seriously, and so does STA Travel. It's our way of sustaining your trust in STA travel and our products and services. This means we will take all reasonable measures to ensure your information is secure and have implemented technology for this purpose.

 **In summary** STA Travel is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on our sites to make our service the best they can be and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

 **Your consent** By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by STA Travel.

 **Feedback** STA Travel welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please contact us if you have any queries via the links below. STA Travel reserves the right to alter our privacy policy, as business needs requires. Any alterations to this policy will be posted on our website in a timely manner. Send an email to [marketing.sg@statravel.com](mailto:marketing.sg@statravel.com)
